<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Insight Creative, Inc.</title>
    <description></description>
    <link></link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Can Music Impact a Buying Decision?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/can-music-impact-a-buying-decision.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Power of Music&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am very passionate about music. Music moves me, makes me feel nostalgic and incites a lot of emotion in me—which could make me connect with a brand that uses music I like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s why companies pick popular or familiar music because there’s a better chance of people liking it or connecting with it. Popular bands are licensing their music to big brands more than ever before. I wonder, is it a cash grab by these bands or are they really into the various brands? I’m guessing it’s a cash grab, and that doesn’t make me feel good about these bands or brands. It feels like they are “selling out,” and that doesn’t sit well with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That said, when music really fits a video and enhances it—like these two below do very well—the spots get me pumped up. In these cases I like the music; it gets me excited and I do actually remember the brands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Motorhead is featured in a new KIA commercial.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0b1bNb8moSQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Led Zeppelin is featured by Cadillac in their new commercial.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/gpD7f8gWgDg&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While music may not &lt;em&gt;make&lt;/em&gt; you buy something, it can help you remember a brand, which it did for me in these cases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand Walmart using the Bee Gees, Whitesnake, The Who and other popular music is interesting. It gets me to look up from my phone to see what’s on TV, but then I’m left disappointed when I see it’s Walmart, a brand which I already have a negative feeling toward. Does this music help change my mind about the Walmart brand? Not really.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/P4IwOujzRiM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/7GA0xPJcxZ8&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NFL Monday Night Football music makes me RUN to the TV because I love football, and to me that song means football is going to start. It has longevity with the brand as well. Hearing it for so many years brings recognition to another level. In this case, for me, it works really well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, do ads with music perform better than ads without? According to a Nielsen evaluation from a few years ago they do:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/can-music-impact-a-buying-decision-2.gif&quot; alt=&quot;The Nielsen Company, I Second That Notion: The Power of Music in Advertising&quot; /&gt;
&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot; href=&quot;http://www.nielsen.com/us/en/insights/news/2015/i-second-that-emotion-the-emotive-power-of-music-in-advertising.html&quot;&gt;I Second That Emotion: The Emotive Power of Music in Advertising—The Nielsen Company_&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, for me, the &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt; music with the &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt; brand can really enhance an ad and help you remember it. However, when music is just picked because it was popular and doesn’t really fit the brand, it just doesn’t work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>//blog/can-music-impact-a-buying-decision.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//blog/can-music-impact-a-buying-decision.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Insight Creative, Inc. Hires Account Executive Brian Brost</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Insight Creative, Inc. recently hired Brian Brost as account executive. As a part of the business development and account management team, Brost will be responsible for expanding the agency’s client list, meeting the needs of existing clients and managing the daily progress of projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/brian-brost.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Brian Brost&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brost brings over 20 years of account management experience to his new role at Insight Creative. He held account executive positions at local television stations FOX11 and NBC26 as well as at Humana Insurance Company. Brost holds a degree in hospitality and tourism management from University of Wisconsin—Stout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insight Creative, Inc.—successfully serving clients since 1988—is a Green Bay-based advertising agency offering complete in-house creative and strategic marketing communications expertise for consumer, business and industrial clients.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//blog/insight-creative-inc-hires-account-executive-brian-brost.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//blog/insight-creative-inc-hires-account-executive-brian-brost.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Internet of Things - The Future is Now</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/internet-of-things.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Internet of Things&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you been hearing about the Internet of Things (IoT)? Like me, have you wondered what it means? It’s a somewhat generic sounding term that packs a ton of meaning for our future as a society, as marketers and as salespeople. What exactly is IoT? In short, it’s the interconnectedness of objects: your phone talking to your car’s radio, setting your home DVR from your office, or your Fitbit posting your workout results directly on social media. (By the way, on behalf of all your social contacts, if you’re doing this please stop). Make no mistake, this is a BIG thing. Qualcomm Technologies analysts estimate that IoT applications could have a total economic impact of up to 11 trillion dollars annually by 2025.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to SmartInsight.com, it is expected there will be 75 billion connected devices worldwide by 2020. That means there will be ten times as many devices able to talk to one another as people on Earth. It only makes sense that these devices start taking over some of our annoying daily tasks and interactions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/internet-of-things-hp-printer.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Internet of Things&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, IoT has alleviated one of my small but bothersome life tasks—ordering printer ink. For the past twenty years my husband and I have battled over replacing our printer ink. Stressful late night presentation deadlines were frequently exacerbated by running out of ink. Keeping a back-up supply on hand was expensive, required us to actually locate that supply at 1:30 a.m. and—when we did remember to purchase replacement cartridges—we’d fight about replacing only the black, which had run out, or (foolishly, ahem) replacing all the color cartridges at the same time in the name of convenience. Now, since we enrolled in &lt;a href=&quot;http://www8.hp.com/us/en/instant-ink/overview.html&quot;&gt;HP Instant Ink&lt;/a&gt;, our internet-enabled printer monitors our usage as well as its own ink levels, then orders replacement ink when levels get low. And best of all, we’re not even aware it’s happening until the ink shows up in the mailbox. If only all marriage issues could be easily solved with a recurring monthly charge of $2.99 on my credit card!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/internet-of-things-charmin.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Internet of Things&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Products that market and actually purchase more of themselves are one of the most significant ways IoT can impact brands. Just like my experience with HP Instant Ink, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/s/ref=sr_pg_1?rh=i%3Aaps%2Ck%3Adash+button&amp;amp;keywords=dash+button&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1505229711&quot;&gt;Amazon’s Dash Buttons&lt;/a&gt; are making life easier for consumers and brands every day. These handy little buttons can be affixed all over our house and allow you to reorder products with the press of a button. Grabbing the last roll of toilet paper? No problem if you have a Charmin Dash Button in the bathroom cabinet. Just give it a press and you’ve reordered TP from Amazon. (Then, if you have Amazon Prime, it will be delivered to your home for free in two days. Try explaining that to your grandmother!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clearly, the world is becoming more interconnected. And this interconnectedness provides some exciting opportunities for brands and their marketing partners.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//blog/internet-of-things-the-future-is-now.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//blog/internet-of-things-the-future-is-now.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Influencer Marketing - Risks and Rewards</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/influencer-marketing-risks-and-rewards.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Influencer Marketing: Risks and Rewards&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you work in advertising or PR, you’ve probably heard the phrase “influencer marketing” a lot lately. If you’re a high-profile consumer brand, you’re probably already doing it or have been for some time. It’s a term that has spread like wildfire and has extended outside the world of professional communicators and into mainstream media with stories of epic failures &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.inc.com/shane-barker/the-fyre-festival-marketing-disaster-2-important-i.html&quot;&gt;(like the infamous celebrity-stacked Fyre Festival)&lt;/a&gt; or major successes (such as the sky-rocketing love for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.vogue.com/article/rose-trend-tipping-point&quot;&gt;rosé wine with hashtag #RoseAllDay&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/ajagrawal/2016/12/27/why-influencer-marketing-will-explode-in-2017/#26af3fd420a9&quot;&gt;According to Forbes&lt;/a&gt;, a recent survey revealed 84% of marketers plan on executing at least one influencer marketing campaign this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may hear it often, but what exactly is “influencer marketing”? Is it best applied to large national brands and A-list celebrities? What type of businesses can benefit most from influencer marketing? Can this approach be replicated for small business? These are the questions I ask myself on behalf of our clients when a “new” marketing trend rises to the social surface. Here’s my breakdown of influencer marketing, plus the risks and rewards associated with the social media trend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intro to Influencer Marketing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
It’s difficult to pin-point a simple definition of influencer marketing. Instead, here’s a list of what it is and what it most certainly is not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;INFLUENCER MARKETING IS …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a partnership.&lt;/strong&gt; A business or organization collaborates on social media with a well-known personality or “influencer” to promote a cause, product, event, brand, mission, etc. that aligns with the influencer’s passion or expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;mutually beneficial.&lt;/strong&gt; Both the marketer and the influencer should see benefits from the campaign. A brand gains access to a large network of loyal trusting followers and the influencer benefits from being the first to share information about new, exciting or valuable products.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;an on-going effort.&lt;/strong&gt; While some influencers carry more star power than others, it still takes time for them to build genuine interest with their audience about a certain project or product. Much like other organic social efforts, successful influencer marketing campaigns require an investment of time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;INFLUENCER MARKETING IS NOT …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;appointing a spokesperson.&lt;/strong&gt; Social influencers are not always A-list celebrities. Usually they are the most passionate and most credible people in the industry. They also promote products solely on social, not traditional media.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;over-promotional.&lt;/strong&gt; The best influencers seamlessly integrate messages and photos of a product or brand right into their regular content without appearing salesy.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;fake.&lt;/strong&gt; To be successful, the influencer must have a genuine interest in the product, cause or project. Their followers are looking to them for advice, recommendations or expertise only on certain topics. The product and the audience must align.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WEIGHING RISKS AND REWARDS OF INFLUENCER MARKETING …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Risk:&lt;/strong&gt; Influencers can be unpredictable. They could go off-script with your product, inadvertently make false claims or post something that affects the reputation of your product.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reward:&lt;/strong&gt; Your product or cause could be instantly catapulted into the social spotlight as a “trendy” item, depending on your influencer’s passion and popularity.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Risk:&lt;/strong&gt; Your product could have the potential to harm the influencer’s reputation. If your product is recalled, or your company experiences a failure, the addition of several active social followers could amplify your PR problem.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reward:&lt;/strong&gt; You can gain access to millions of followers on social media without employing paid media.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Risk:&lt;/strong&gt; Influencers are human. Therefore, tragedy, death or unexpected circumstances can always derail a campaign—even with the most reliable influencers.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reward:&lt;/strong&gt; Your brand will earn instant credibility with an audience that already has trust established with the influencer.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you weigh the risks and rewards of influencer marketing, you may also consider your target audience. If you’re marketing to heavy users of social media (teens, moms, and other active online groups), it truly may be the best way to reach your target market. In that case, the rewards outweigh the risks. Have plenty ideas for attainable influencers? Even better! Just make sure to properly vet influencers, create a campaign plan that both parties can agree upon, and keep it real!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have more questions about influencer marketing? &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:media@insightcreative.com&quot;&gt;Contact our team today.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//blog/influencer-marketing-risks-and-rewards.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//blog/influencer-marketing-risks-and-rewards.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pinpoint Your Target with Geofencing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/pinpoint-your-target-with-geofencing.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pinpoint Your Target with Geofencing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the latest sporting event you attended, did you see an ad on your smartphone promoting a nearby restaurant inviting you to stop in after the game? You might have thought it was a little creepy this restaurant knew you were there, but it’s called geofencing—an effective marketing tactic if executed correctly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Geofencing is a location-based digital marketing tactic that lets marketers place ads targeted towards smartphone users in a defined geographic area. You chose a radius around a location, and when someone enters that space, they are served an ad while using the internet on their mobile device. It can be used for both business-to-consumer (B2C) and business-to-business (B2B) marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, as customers walk into a shopping mall, retailers can target people with offers and coupons. A car dealership can target people when they visit a competitor down the street. Exhibitors at a trade show can use geofencing to target attendees, improve brand awareness and traffic to your booth or website, which in turn generates leads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some tips to effectively use geofencing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep your geofence small.&lt;/strong&gt; A small business dentist should not geofence a large metro area because he may get calls from more patients than he can take on. Instead, he should stick to the neighborhood or suburb around his office.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your message should be relevant.&lt;/strong&gt; Based on the time of day, day of the week, time of year or geographic location, your message needs to make sense. If your restaurant is booked solid for dinner but your lunch crowd is sparse, geofence around your location before lunch time to get people looking for a place to eat.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a clear call to action (and make it a good one.)&lt;/strong&gt; It’s one thing to notify people about your location, but it’s another to have an incentive to come to your business. Provide discounts or offers to bring people to you and have it be attractive enough so people act on it.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Measure campaign results.&lt;/strong&gt; Look at results in real time to determine if it’s a successful campaign or if some tweaks need to be made. Perhaps the creative isn’t strong enough or the area you’re geofencing isn’t quite right. Analyze the results to help determine future campaign strategies.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have more questions about geofencing? &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:media@insightcreative.com&quot;&gt;Contact our team today.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//blog/pinpoint-your-target-with-geofencing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//blog/pinpoint-your-target-with-geofencing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reach Your Customers with Research</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/reach-your-customers-with-research.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Reach your customers with research&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When someone starts a business, they do research to shape their marketing approach. Who will need their products? What is their target audience? What are their customers’ behaviors? How will they best attract them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then the business doors open. Hopefully the customers respond and the business succeeds. The years go by as they tend to the day-to-day operations of the company until one day, they realize their customers’ needs have evolved and they no longer know who they’re servicing. That begs the question … when was the last time you checked in with your prospects? Do you even know who your ideal customer is anymore?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you’ve been in business for five years, 50 years or 100 years, it’s important to review your customer base every three to five years (and the good news is you don’t need a fancy research firm.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use these simple tips to make new discoveries about your target audience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Talk with Your Employees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
If your business has multiple locations, schedule an annual tour to visit all the locations. Talk to the local employees and ask them about their customer interactions, the feedback they receive, note any observations they make and get their recommendations. Your own employees may be your biggest research asset.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use FREE Resources&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Check in with local chamber organizations, school districts, visitor and convention bureaus and tourism groups. These groups utilize a vast amount of resources compiling relevant data. Use this to your advantage and tap into area demographics, economic trends, housing growth reports, new business goals and more.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analyze the Competition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Compare your offers, products and services to your competitors. Are your offers on par with those around you? If not, do you have good reasoning for the differentiation?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research Online&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Review your business’ online reputation. What responses are you receiving on review sites, social media and your website? Are you noticing a reoccurring theme that you need to address?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reassess Your Goals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Review your sales growth or decline. Is this meeting or exceeding expectations? If not, you’re likely missing something in which case you need to go back and review tips 1-4 above.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s no such thing as too much research. Continuing to do the work will help you make sure you’re effectively reaching the right target audience—you’ll see the results in your bottom line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have more questions about researching your customer base? &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:media@insightcreative.com&quot;&gt;Contact our experts!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//blog/reach-your-customers-with-research.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//blog/reach-your-customers-with-research.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Appeal to the Eyes&amp;mdash;Advertising on Pinterest and Instagram</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/appeal-to-the-eyes-advertising-on-pinterest-and-instagram.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Advertising on Pinterest and Instagram&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social media advertising options seem to grow monthly. Everywhere you look there is a new platform to place ads; but which ones are right for you and your business or product? Let’s take a closer look at paid advertising on visual-driven platforms such as Instagram and Pinterest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;instagram&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram is a social media platform a lot like Facebook, probably because Instagram is owned and operated by the creative minds at Facebook. I appreciate the solid targeting features of Facebook, and now those same features lend themselves to Instagram too!  In a nutshell, the difference between Instagram and Facebook is that Instagram is a far more visually-driven social media platform with highly engaging ads that tend to hit a younger audience than Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, the first obvious question to ask yourself … is your target demographic on Instagram?  Almost 26% of the Instagram audience is between 18–34 years old and 23% is between 18–24 years old.  This audience is also predominately female. Second question to ask … is your product or service a popular topic on Instagram? At this time, popular topics on Instagram include food, fashion, and films among other things. So, if you said, “Yes!” to either of those questions, Instagram may be a good choice for you. Moving forward, make sure your creative content is aesthetically pleasing. Instagram users prefer visual to text, and you most certainly want to be able to convey your message accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;pinterest&quot;&gt;Pinterest&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pinterest is another platform that skews heavily toward women, but unlike Instagram, appeals to a wider audience, ages 18–64.  Paid advertising on Pinterest happens in the form of “Promoted Pins” which look just like regular pins, but appear in your feed because a business paid for that placement. Most of the 175 million users on Pinterest are not bothered by Promoted Pins, as they seem to blend into pins they are already searching. Pinterest offers a great opportunity to target people who need your product or service with your relevant Promoted Pin content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, with Pinterest you can’t target a particular region or state. This isn’t a big deal for large, national brands that are trying to reach the masses, however, for many small businesses that challenge is a deal breaker. Local businesses need to be able to target the people near them, and it’s just wasted dollars if you can’t target those consumers specifically. (Things change quickly though! This sort of targeting could be in the works for Pinterest down the road.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where to go from here …&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking at all the social media platforms available can be overwhelming—Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, YouTube, LinkedIn, SnapChat, Tumblr, Reddit and more every day. My best advice is to research one established social media channel to start, and if that platform fits your product and audience, give it some honest consideration. Social media can be a strong addition to any advertising campaign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have more questions about social advertising? &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:media@insightcreative.com&quot;&gt;Contact our experts!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//blog/appeal-to-the-eyes-advertising-on-pinterest-and-instagram.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//blog/appeal-to-the-eyes-advertising-on-pinterest-and-instagram.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Play with Creative</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/play-with-creative-design-with-passion.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Design with Passion&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a designer, I’ve come to find that playing and experimenting are some of the most important things I can do. I discover new techniques I didn’t know existed. I learn to look at things from different perspectives and think more critically about how to accomplish them. And, what I think is just as important, I get to enjoy that spark of energy that doing something new and fun brings. It’s that same feeling I got when I first started doing graphic design in high school, and it’s what helps keep me motivated and working in my field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes I go online and look for tutorials on how to make interesting and cool things. The end result might not be something that I would actually ever create for a client, but learning the process and the techniques to create it brings new and fresh ideas and adds more knowledge under my belt that I can use when the right project comes along. Other times I’ll just jump into a program I feel like improving in and just start playing with tools that I’ve never used in it before. I’ve made many terrible graphics doing this, but I’ve learned more about what’s available for me to use and how to use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, all I’m trying to say is this: &lt;strong&gt;Play with creative&lt;/strong&gt;, it will keep your passion ignited. Set some time to experiment, have fun, and learn new things, because I think you’ll find yourself happier as a creative person, and you’ll grow your skillset even further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some experiments and things I’ve done for fun to develop my skills!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- ![Play With Creative](/img/blog/play-with-creative-design-with-passion.jpg)  --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;wistia_embed wistia_async_cudcnh4olu popover=true popoverAnimateThumbnail=true&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;height:500px;width:100%&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/play-with-creative-snow-environment.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Snow Environment Rendering&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;3D rendering of a snow environment&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/play-with-creative-towel-render.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Towel Rendering&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;3D rendering of a towel&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/play-with-creative-space-abstract.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Abstract Space Rendering&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;3D abstract rendering of space&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/play-with-creative-abstract-sphere.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Abstract Sphere Rendering&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;3D abstract rendering of an illuminated sphere&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/play-with-creative-cherry-blossoms.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cherry Blossom Rendering&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;3D rendering of cherry blossoms&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/play-with-creative-easter-logo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Easter Logo&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Insight Easter logo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/play-with-creative-tyler.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lighting Exploration&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Photography lighting exploration&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/play-with-creative-tyler-two.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lighting Exploration Two&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Photography lighting exploration&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//blog/play-with-creative.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//blog/play-with-creative.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>B2B vs B2C - What You Need to Dominate Social Media</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;wistia_embed wistia_async_ga7iqrq14y popover=true popoverAnimateThumbnail=true&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;height:500px;width:100%&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video Transcription&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone, it’s Jennifer with Insight Creative. Every business struggles with finding—or even creating—the right content for their audience. There are hundreds of different articles, tips and methods of doing so, but what’s the best answer? Today I’m going to share the most ideal content for social media for both business-to-business and business-to-consumer companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First, let’s go over business-to-consumer, aka B2C.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a business who targets everyday customers, such as a restaurant or retail, user generated content is key. Let’s say you’re a local coffee shop who also sells merchandise. Your customers share photos of their cool latte art or a new branded t-shirt they just bought. Sharing or reposting this content on your social media platforms will encourage others to share—or visit your shop—and friends and family who see this on their news feeds will be more likely to engage than before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another type of content that’s ideal for a B2C business is community-building. Community-building content is about getting your customers involved—with more than just products or services. Our client, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rivervalleybank.com/&quot;&gt;River Valley Bank&lt;/a&gt;, is very involved in the communities they serve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;River Valley Bank focuses on getting customers to participate in local events to
help each other build stronger communities. From brat frys and volunteering to raising awareness and donations, River Valley Bank’s community-building content is about what’s happening in the community and how others can help. It’s their way of saying “Hey, let’s get out there and make a difference.” And people remember that River Valley Bank is a key contributor to giving back to the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now let’s focus on business-to-business, aka B2B.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a business who targets other businesses, such as a commercial builder, a logistics management company—or even some ad agencies—providing solutions to problems is key.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you identify what your audience’s pain points are, share the solutions. Remember—don’t make it all about you! The goal is to provide the best information, not promote that your business is the best solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s use this video as an example. We’re sharing the best information on what content your business should be using on social media. We’re not promoting ourselves to solve these problems for you … we’re here as a trusted resource.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another great way to reach your B2B audience is using customer testimonials. In today’s world, social proof is everything. From reviews to word-of-mouth, people value the opinion of others who are just like them. When you share customer testimonials, it allows your audience to see what others truly think of your business. It also provides some context as to why they like your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re a B2B business or a B2C business, you now know what types of content will attract your social media audience. Thanks for watching!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//blog/b2b-vs-b2b-what-you-need.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//blog/b2b-vs-b2b-what-you-need.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Media Director/Account Executive Andy VanRemortel Graduates from Leadership Green Bay</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Insight Creative Account Executive/Media Director Andy VanRemortel graduated in the class of 2017 from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.greatergbc.org/programs/leadership/leadership-green-bay&quot;&gt;Leadership Green Bay&lt;/a&gt; this May. The community-based program led by the Green Bay Chamber of Commerce admits 45 outstanding area professionals each year and runs from September to May.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/blog/media-director-andy-vanremortel-graduates.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Andy VanRemortel at Leadership Green Bay&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through the course of the program, professionals attend monthly meetings focusing on a variety of topics including government, economic development, education, health and human services and more equipping them to lead programs that affect change in our communities. For the final phase of the program, students assemble into teams, choose a local cause or problem to address, and develop sustainable solutions to ultimately contribute to the betterment of greater Green Bay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VanRemortel’s team selected the Dr. Rosa Minoka-Hill School for their final project. As an alternative K-12 school, the Minoka-Hill School serves students with a continuum of unique learning needs. Students are provided support to overcome personal challenges with the goal of transitioning back to their neighborhood or choice school, and ultimately graduating college, to be career and community ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Van Remortel’s team identified that, due to a lack of funds, the school has never held a formal graduation. Their Leadership Green Bay team developed a sustainable graduation ceremony for the school that now includes caps and gowns, two $1,000 scholarships for the next five years and a venue (Green Bay East High School).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Leadership Green Bay is a fantastic program,” said VanRemortel. “It helps you look outside your regular day-to-day life and realize your community really needs you.” While completing the program, VanRemortel became inspired to extend his leadership talents beyond the duties of the program. He recently accepted positions on the board of directors for Golden House and the board of appeals for the City of De Pere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are YOU a Leader?&lt;/strong&gt;
The Green Bay Chamber of Commerce is currently taking applications for Leadership Green Bay Class of 2018. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.greatergbc.org/media/428896/lgb%20app%20class%20of%202018.pdf&quot;&gt;Apply now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//blog/media-director-account-executive-andy-vanremortel-graduates-from-leadership-green-bay.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//blog/media-director-account-executive-andy-vanremortel-graduates-from-leadership-green-bay.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
